Guide to the Russell Cornell Leffingwell Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1917-1960; Series I; 3 linear feet (7 boxes)
  - G (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Gay, Charles R., 1937 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - George, Walter F., 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Gifford, T.J. Carlyle, (*), 1942-1956, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 47-50)
  - Gilbert, S. Parker, Jr., (*), 1920-1922 May (Box 2, Folder 51-57)
  - Gilbert, S. Parker, Jr., (*), 1922 June-1923 Nov, 1924-1928 (Box 3, Folder 58-61)
  - Gilbert, S. Parker, Jr., 1931-1932, 1935-1937 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Glass, Carter, (*), 1918, 1920-1924, 1927, 1929, 1931-1936, 1938-1939, 1941-1942, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 64-67)
  - Green, William R., (*), 1921-1923 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Grenfell, E. C., 1925, 1929-1933 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - H (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Hanes, John W., (*), 1939, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Harding, Warren G., 1920-1921 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Harrison, George L., (*), 1929, 1932, 1937, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Haskell, Henry J., 1935, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Hilles, Charles D., 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Hines, Walker D., 1921 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Hoover, Herbert, (*), 1921, 1928-1929, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Hopkinson, Edward, Jr. (*), 1932-1934 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Houston, D.F., (*), 1920-1921 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Hull, Cordell, (*), 1923, 1931-1933, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Humphrey, George M., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - I-J (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Jay, N. Dean, (*), 1925, 1927-1928, 1931-1935 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - K (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Kefauver, Estes, (*), 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Kelley, Nicholas, (*), 1920-1922, 1930, 1936, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Kellogg, Frank B., (*), 1920-1921 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Kelsey, Clarence H., 1923 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Keynes, John Maynard, (*), 1922, 1942, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - L (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Lamont, Thomas Stilwell, 1935-1937, 1940, 1950-1953, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Lamont, Thomas W., (*), 1920-1943 (Box 4, Folder 92-100)
  - Lamont, Thomas W., (*), 1944-1948 (Box 5, Folder 101-103)
  - Layton, Dorothy, (*), 1943-1959 (Box 5, Folder 104-105)
  - Layton, Walter, (*), 1927-1928, 1930-1932, 1938, 1940-1942, 1944-1947, 1950-1952, 1956, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Lippmann, Walter, (*), 1929-1937, 1939-1945, 1947-1951, 1953-1955, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Lippmann, Walter, (*), 1932 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Lippmann, Walter, (*), 1933-1935 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Lippmann, Walter, (*), 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Lippmann, Walter, (*), 1939-1942 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Lippmann, Walter, (*), 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Lippmann, Walter, (*), 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Lippmann, Walter, (*), 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Lippmann, Walter, (*), 1951, 1953-1955, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Lovett, Robert A., (*), 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - M (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - McAdoo, William Gibbs, (*), 1917-1918, 1921-1923, 1925, 1927, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - McCabe, Thomas B., (*), 1948-1951 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - McCloy, John J., (*), 1947-1949 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - McFadden, Louis T., 1921 (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - Malbry, Walter, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Meyer, Eugene, Jr., (*), 1920, 1926, 1929, 1931-1932, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Meyer, J.M., 1937, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Mills, Ogden L., (*), 1922, 1932, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Morgan, J.P., (*), 1923, 1925, 1929, 1931-1933, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, Jr., (*), 1934, 1936-1938, 1941-1944 (Box 6, Folder 128-129)
  - Morrow, Dwight W., (*), 1925-1928, 1930-1931 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - N (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Nimitz, Chester W., (*), 1951 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Norman, Montagu C., (*), 1925, 1929, 1932, 1943-1948 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - Noyes, C. Reinold, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - Nye, Gerald, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - O (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - P (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Peacock, Edward R., (*), 1932, 1944-1947 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Platt, Edmund (*), 1920, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - R (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Rathbone, Albert, 1921-1922 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Rathbone, Albert (*), 1924-1928, 1931, 1934-1936 (Box 6, Folder 142-143)
  - Raushenbush, Stephen, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Rist, Charles, (*), 1927-1928, 1931, 1933, 1940, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., (*), 1932-1934 (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1940-1943 (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Ruml, Beardsley, 1944, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - S (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Sachs, Alexander (*), 1934-1937, 1940-1943, 1946-1948, 1950-1952, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - Salter, Arthur, 1948, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 151)
  - Scherman, Harry, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - Seay, George J., 1934 (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Sherley, Swagar, 1933-1934 (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - Smith, Vivian, 1932, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Snyder, John W., 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Sproul, Allan, 1940-1941, 1943-1944, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - Sproul, Allan, 1948-1949, 1951, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Stettinius, Edward R., Jr., (*), 1943, 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Strauss, Albert, 1922, 1925-1926 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Strong, Benjamin, (*), 1919-1922, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 161-162)
  - T (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Thomas, Elmer, (*), 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Truman, Harry S., (*), 1948-1951 (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - w (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Wasson, R.G., (*), 1935-1937, 1939-1945, 1947-1948, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 168-169)
  - Whigham, C.J., 1927, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Whitney, George, 1942, 1944-1945, 1947, 1950, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - Wilson Woodrow, 1917, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 172)
- Memoranda, 1922-1958; Series II; 0.25; (1 box)
  Memoranda are arranged in chronological order.
  - 1922-1923 (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - 1932-1945 (Box 8, Folder 174-178)
  - 1948-1949 (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - 1951, 1953, 1956-1958 (Box 8, Folder 180)
- Writings and speeches, 1919 - 1958; Series III; .5 linear feet (2 boxes)
  Writings and speeches are arranged together in chronological order.
  - 1919-1921 (Box 9, Folder 181)
  - 1922, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 182)
  - 1930-1931, 1933-1936 (Box 9, Folder 183)
  - 1939-1941 (Box 9, Folder 184)
  - 1943-1948 (Box 10, Folder 185)
  - 1949-1950, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 186)
  - 1955, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 187)
- Photographs, memorabilia, and writings about Russell Cornell Leffingwell, Circa 1883 - 1903, 1979; Series IV; .75 linear feet (2 boxes)
  - Photographs of family and friends, Circa 1883-1901 (Box 11, Folder 188)
  - Scrapbook, Circa 1898-1903 (Box 11, Folder 189)
  - Selected Letters by R.C. Leffingwell, ed. by Edward Pulling, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 190)
  - "Russell C. Leffingwell". Sketch for the Dictionary of American Biography by Stephen A. Schuker, [1979?] (Box 12, Folder 191)